Liyana Bukhari

765 Main Road,Tucson, AZ 97531 I.bukhari@myemail.com (753) 357-7531

Diligent and professional accounting assistant with a 2-year track record for providing outstanding accountancy support for a Leading flooring retailer. Advanced record-keeping and auditing skills with a talent for detecting and rectifying accounting discrepancies. Collaborative and efficient working style with a proven ability to process payroll independently and accurately.

Education

Associate of Science in Business Administration (Accounting)

Pima Community College, Tucson. AZ September 2017-June 2019

Key Skills

- Sales tax reporting
- Financial auditing
- ♦ Payroll
- Time management and organization
- Excellent verbal and written communication skills
- Attention to detail

Professional Experience

Accounting Assistant

Carpet One Floor and Home, Tucson, AZ | July 2019 - Present

- Assist senior accountants with generating sales tax reports and performing yearly audits, receiving praise 4x during performance reviews for collaboration and communication skills
- Perform monthly payroll processing for branch employees and update employee information to ensure payment accuracy
- Scrupulously follow company policies and state and federal guidelines, maintaining 100% compliance over 2 years
- Complete tasks accurately to tight deadlines, meeting 99.5% of time-sensitive targets in 2020

Sales Associate

Five Below, Tucson, AZ | September 2016-July 2019

- Assisted with cash balancing tasks and identified discrepancies with 98.7% accuracy throughout employment
- Designed and created attractive merchandising displays, boosting sales of promoted lines by 32% in December 2018
- Acted up as assistant manager to cover staff absence when required, overseeing and motivating a team of up to 8 colleagues
- Answered customer queries efficiently over the telephone and in writing